{
    "subject": "Denis_H\u00e9roux",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Val\u00e9rie",
    "human_readable": "Denis H\u00e9roux created Val\u00e9rie.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9145592451095581,
            "question": "Why do you think Denis H\u00e9roux created Val\u00e9rie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.848138153553009,
            "question": "What did Denis H\u00e9roux create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8181840777397156,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Denis H\u00e9roux and Val\u00e9rie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8039745688438416,
            "question": "Who created Val\u00e9rie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7723850011825562,
            "question": "Who is Denis H\u00e9roux?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7099354267120361,
            "question": "What is the name of the person who created Val\u00e9rie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6855635046958923,
            "question": "Are there any other creations by Denis H\u00e9roux?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5061087012290955,
            "question": "What might Val\u00e9rie be used for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4302324056625366,
            "question": "Is Val\u00e9rie a person, a place, or something else?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41118401288986206,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Val\u00e9rie?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Denis H\u00e9roux created Val\u00e9rie.",
            "html": "yago_7708_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Val\u00e9rie a person, a place, or something else?",
            "html": "yago_7708_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might Val\u00e9rie be used for?",
            "html": "yago_7708_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other creations by Denis H\u00e9roux?",
            "html": "yago_7708_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7708_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7708_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7708_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7708_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7708_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7708_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7708_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7708_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7708_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7708_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Denis H\u00e9roux created Val\u00e9rie.\" Specifically, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_7708/re-ranker-msmarco/18.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_7708/re-ranker-msmarco/23.txt both mention that Denis H\u00e9roux directed the film \"Val\u00e9rie,\" which was released in 1969."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}